YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴： godwuwen
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： 小黑  独醉  YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第四集
没想到我居然会接受心理治疗
I can't believe I'm talking to a therapist.
我平时不太愿意表露感情
Well, usually, I'm not the touchy-feely,
属于喜怒不形于色的那种
talk-about-your-emotions type,
但目前形势严峻  我要成熟一点
but with this, I just had to be a big enough person
勇敢承认自己需要帮助
to admit that I need help.
哈  原来成熟就是这种感觉啊
Huh. I guess this is what growing up feels like.
这是法院强制的心理治疗
This is court-mandated therapy.
你袭击了一位女性  记得不
You assaulted a woman.
就那破事儿啊
That silly thing.
好吧  我们来谈吧
I guess we can talk about that.
祸根是几个月之前就埋下了
It all began a few months ago.
故事的主人公叫巴尼  我的前男友
There's this guy, Barney. We used to date.
分手后  我撮合他和我的女同事诺拉在一起
I set him up with this girl I work with, Nora.
巴尼使出浑身解数
Barney was working hard
努力去证明自己是绝世好男友
to prove he was real boyfriend material.
所以呢  我一整周都坐在那儿  眼睁睁看着
So, all week, I had to sit there watching him...
他送花
send flowers...
送巧克力
chocolates...
送气球
balloons.
终于有一天
Then one day...
我听说巴尼今天没送你东西
I heard Barney didn't send anything today.
帕崔斯说可能他有新欢了
Patrice said maybe he met somebody else.
这八婆管不住嘴  对吧
She's such a bitch, right?
当男人爱上女人 *
* When a man loves a woman
他的心将完全被她占据 *
* Can't keep his mind on nothin' else
绝世好男友啊
He's so dreamy.
帕崔斯  你给我闭嘴
Nobody asked you, Patrice!
不好意思
I'm sorry.
你肯定认为我无药可救了  是吧
You must already think that I'm a horrible person.
罗宾  我的治疗对象有很多是心理扭曲的罪犯
Robin, many of my patients are disturbed felons.
上周  有人还给我寄了一包他自己的米田共
Last week, one of them mailed me a bag of his feces.
不过往好的方面想  他至少记得我的生日
On the plus side, he remembered my birthday.
你算好的了
You're doing fine.
终于  我忍无可忍
Well, finally, I-I just couldn't take it anymore.
于是理智线断了
I snapped.
当男人  当一个男人  当这个男人 *
* When a man, when a man, when this man
爱上了这个女人 *
* Loves this woman
然后你怒火中烧  对其施暴
And that's when the assault occurred?
不算是吧
Not exactly.
所以你躲在桌底  边借酒浇愁
So, you're drunk under a desk,
边狂吃偷来的巧克力
binge-eating stolen chocolates.
天啊  我的形象顿时荡然无存  对吧
Boy, I am not coming across great here, am I?
现在我们不讨论你的形象
This is not about how you're coming across.
不过的确如此
But no.
为了使整件事更合理化
Okay, well, for this story to make sense,
我得插入我的朋友马修和莉莉的故事
I have to tell you about my friends Marshall and Lily.
这酒看上去不错
The wine looks good.
孕妇不许喝酒
Pregnant women can't drink alcohol.
不会啊  我的医生说
No, my doctor says it's okay
偶尔喝个一两口没事
to have a sip of wine every now and then.
是吗
Really?
桑娅医生太好了
Dr. Sonya's great.
每次你问她可不可以吃什么东西时  她总是说
Whenever you ask her if you can have something, she's, like...
亲  就一点点哦
Just a little bit.
慢着  桑娅医生应该不会允许你吃寿司吧
Wait, Dr. Sonya doesn't let you have sushi, does she?
亲  就一点点哦
Just a little bit.
她还让你吃玉米条啊
You're allowed to have Cheetos?
膨化食品啊
Cheeto..
亲  就一点点哦
Ah, just a little bit.
你们不介意我复查一下这医生说的话吧
You mind if I double-check some of this stuff?
以防万一嘛
Just in case.
我是说  身为"护子队"的一员
I mean, it's the least I could do
这也算是聊表寸心吧
as part of Team Baby.
"护子队"  哇  接下来呢
"Team Baby"? Whoa. What's next,
人手一件特制的劣质T恤吗
like, cheesy matching T-shirts?
不是
No.
罗宾  连环杀手都能带我去浅墓穴几个来回了
Robin, I've had serial killers lead me to shallow graves
你这还没进入主题呢
faster than you're telling this story.
好啦
Okay!
我越来越无法忍受与诺拉共事
Look, it was getting impossible for me to be around Nora,
所以当有摆脱她的好机会出现时
So when an opportunity to get rid of her presented itself...
桑迪有话说时间
It's Sandy time!
来来来  都听好
Huddle up, gang.
两件事  第一
Two things: Somebody stole
有人从我办公室里偷了一瓶超贵的酒
a very expensive bottle of wine from my office...
第二  我需要一个制片人去法国报道八国峰会的新闻
2:I need a producer to cover the G8 Summit in France.
诺拉可以去
Nora will do it!
虽然我资格比较老  不过
I mean, I know I have seniority, but...
我的意思也是让诺拉去
I was gonna ask Nora anyway.
谢谢你这么支持我  罗宾
Thanks for the support, Robin.
这个机会太棒了
This is huge for me.
你确定吗  桑迪
Are, are you sure about this, Sandy?
我可是资格老经验足啊
I do have seniority.
当然确定咯  诺拉太棒了
Oh, I'm sure. Nora's amazing.
我还想跟她滚床单呢
I want to have sex with her.
先是巴尼离你而去
To deal with that rejection from Barney,
现在连你老板也不要你
not to mention your boss...
你一定很郁闷
must've really hurt.
我们来深入分析你这些情绪吧
Why don't we dig into those emotions?
所以马修和莉莉在桑娅医生的办公室
So Marshall and Lily were at Dr. Sonya's office...
太神奇了吧
It's fascinating
原来我对阴道的了解是那么肤浅
how profoundly little I know about vaginas.
进来
Come in.
泰德  你来干嘛
Ted, what are you doing here?!
这位"医生"允许的事
I checked up on all the stuff
我都查过了  她是错的
this "Doctor" Says is okay, and she's wrong.
所以为了宝宝的健康成长  哥要出马了
So, for the health of this baby, I'm stepping in.
这个叫泰德的人好像是需要一些心理治疗了
Sounds like this Ted guy could benefit from some therapy.
他绝对需要
Oh, he definitely could.
这样的庸医是无法接受的
This is unacceptable.
不好意思  我们要换医生
I'm sorry, we're gonna have to find a new doctor.
-伙计们  为了我们孩子的健康  -关你什么事
-Guys, for the health of our baby, - Our?
我们得对莉莉吃的每一样东西严加把关
We have to get serious about what Lily is putting in her body.
顺便说一下  生孩子时
Speaking of which, when we deliver,
我们坚决不用麻药
we won't be using any drugs.
滚出去
Get out!
你赶我出去干嘛
Why are you kicking me out?!
因为你总是打扰我们的私密时刻
Because you're always intruding on our intimate moments!
感觉大学时期的恶梦又重新上演了
This is like college all over again!
你们俩把寝室弄得乱糟糟
Man, you guys sure are messy!
地上全是衣服
There's clothes everywhere.
门把手上还有一只袜子
There's even a sock on the door!
门把手挂个袜子是全球通用的信号
A sock on the door is a universal code
意思是"请勿打扰"
for "We need some space."
那时候你不该打扰  现在也一样
We needed it back then, and we need it now.
拜托  我们可是铁三角
Come on! We're a trio!
我们一直都是铁三角
We've always been a trio!
我们是蝙蝠侠和罗宾  以及管家阿福
We're right up there with Batman and Robin and Alfred.
出去
Out!
我们是罗密欧与朱丽叶  以及买毒药的药剂师
Romeo and Juliet and the Apothecary.
赶快
Now!
我们是盐和胡椒  以及孜然
Salt and Pepper and Cumin!
上面那个小东西是干嘛的
What's that little guy up there do?
可怜的姑娘
Oh, you poor girl.
罗宾
Robin!
这都是环环相扣的  我保证
It all ties together, I swear.
诺拉准备出发去法国了
So, Nora was about to leave for France.
这要是在不久前
You know, not too long ago,
我还会担心等我走了之后
I would have been worried that if I left you alone,
你会跑去跟某个金发浪女风流快活
you'd be up to no good with some blond bimbo.
但我已经洗心革面了
Oh, I've changed.
我知道  所以说我回来之后
I know, which is why when I get back,
我们将开启感情的新篇章
it's gonna be the start of a new chapter for us.
我们的关系会更近一步  希望这领带就别跟来了
A chapter of me and you and hopefully not that tie.
正中下怀
You got me!
旅途愉快
Have a nice trip!
斯丁森医生  我看了你的广告
Dr. Stinson? I saw your ad,
我是为了免费缩胸咨询而来的
and I'm here for my free breast-reduction consultation.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
太大了吗
Are they too big?
我真不敢相信你还在钓胸大无脑的金发妹
I can't believe you're still running plays on dumb blondes!
我还以为你对诺拉是认真的呢
I thought you were serious about Nora!
我发誓  我真的变乖了
No, I've been good, I swear!
我只是忘记还有个系统没关掉
I just forgot about my BDSes.
-什么系统  -"蠢妞送上门"系统
- BDSes? - Bimbo Delivery Systems.
多年以来
You see, over the years,
我为自己量身定制了多套完美的策略
I've launched a variety of elaborate systems
成功地将女人一个接一个骗上床
that are always working to get me laid.
比如说  那个弹出式广告
Like my pop-up ads.
你好  我是巴尼・斯丁森医生
Oh, hi. I'm Dr. Barney Stinson.
你是否因为胸部过大
Are your really large breasts
而影响到日常生活
making everyday tasks difficult?
谁来救救我们吧
There's just got to be a better way!
救星来了
There is!
我  巴尼・斯汀森医生  将为您限时提供
I, Dr. Barney Stinson, for a limited time only,
免费缩胸咨询服务
can give you a free breast-reduction consultation.
现在就拿起电话吧
Call me.
如果你波涛汹涌得闹不住
If your knockers are just too damn big,
就让我带你脱离苦海吧
I can handle them... it.
居然会有女人相信这种东西
Women actually fell for that?
是啊  这生意一炮打响
Yeah. That business really took off.
广告还在各地播放呢
It played in all kinds of markets.
幸存者们  今天挑战成功的奖品
Okay, survivors, today's reward challenge
巴尼・斯汀森医生提供的
is brought to you by Dr. Barney Stinson's
免费缩胸咨询
Free Breast Reduction Consultations.
我的计划实在是太成功
That scam was so successful,
于是又衍生出了另一个产业
it spawned a related enterprise.
如果你曾被一个勃大茎深的男人骗财骗色
If you've been fooled by a well-endowed man
那人自称自己是医生
who claimed to be a doctor
利用提供免费缩胸咨询服务来行骗
offering free breast-reduction consultations,
来找我吧  阿尼・林森律师
come see me, Arnie Linson, attorney-at-law,
加入我的集体诉讼
and join my class-action suit.
如果你因为玉峰高耸而深受其害
If your giant breasts have been wronged,
就让我来为民除害吧
I can handle them... it.
她们始终飞不出我的手掌心
I got 'em comin' and goin'!
你居然为了骗妞上床费那么多功夫
I can't believe you go to so much trouble to get laid.
就是  有时候我连澡都懒得洗
Yeah, sometimes I don't even have to shower.
姐就喜欢重口味
Mama loves it musky.
我得在诺拉回来前把这些系统都关掉
I gotta shut down all these systems before Nora gets back.
三天内怎么可能办到
How am I gonna do all that in three days?
我会帮你
I'll help you.
或许你应该在你的小板子写上
Maybe you should write on your little chart there:
病人无私地帮助朋友
"Patient selflessly tried to help a friend in need."
首先  这是字谜
First of all, this is a crossword puzzle.
其次  很明显你计划
Secondly, you were clearly planning on using
利用这三天把巴尼抢回去
those three days to steal Barney back.
我是他的朋友  你真不要脸
I am his friend! How dare you!
天啊  你还真以为学富五车就能洞悉人心啊
God, you think you're so smart just because
上过哈佛了不起吗
you went to Harvard
普林斯顿又怎么样
and then Princeton
怎么又是哈佛  好吧  是挺牛的
and then... wow, Harvard again.
好吧  是的
Okay, yes, fine.
我是想着把他抢回去
I was... I was trying to steal him back.
很好  你终于肯打开心扉
This is good. You're finally opening up
谈谈自己的问题了
and talking about yourself,
而不是三句不离马修莉莉
not just what Marshall and Lily were up to.
对哦  马修和莉莉正叠衣服
Oh, yeah, so Marshall and Lily were folding laundry...
我真是犯贱
That one's my fault.
知道吗
You know...
没什么
Never mind.
只是
It's just...
算了
Forget it.
马修  你又不是三岁小孩
Marshall, you're a grown-ass man.
想说什么就说吧
If you want to say something, just say it.
我为泰德感到难过
I feel bad for Ted!
还有如果我老妈在这
And if my mom were here,
她会先问我怎么了
she would ask me what was wrong.
你居然为泰德感到难过
You feel bad for Ted?!
当电灯泡的感觉肯定让他很难受
It's tough feeling like the third wheel.
够了  第一  我肯定泰德没事
Okay, first of all, I'm sure Ted's fine.
谁会加完盐和胡椒  不再加点孜然的
Who eats salt and pepper without cumin?
第二  泰德指责桑娅医生真是太离谱了
Second, Ted is way off base coming after Dr. Sonya.
我们很喜欢她  是吧
We love her! Right?
别告诉我你也怀疑桑娅医生的话
Don't tell me you're doubting Dr. Sonya!
亲  就一点点哦
Just a little bit.
这是什么
What's that thing?
对某些女人来说  这是我父母的骨灰
Well, for some women, it was the ashes of my parents.
对有些来说  是温布尔登的奖杯
For others, it was the trophy from Wimbledon.
信不信由你  对一个波霸傻妞来讲  两者皆是
And believe it or not, for one busty dullard, it was both.
比赛  双波  绝配
Game, enormous set, match.
你好
Hello?
对  多谢回电
Oh, yeah, thanks for calling me back.
巴尼
Uh, Barney,
是港务局的米奇
It's Mitch from the Port Authority.
港务局米奇
Port Authority Mitch.
每当有一个怀揣百老汇梦想的
You'd always call me whenever
纯真乡下女孩下了巴士
a wide-eyed farm girl would get off the bus
你就会及时致电给我
with big dreams of Broadway
可怜的孩子  全然不知所谓的"选角导演"会在试镜时
and no idea what a "Casting director" could legally ask her to do,
合法地要求她又抱又舔
hold or lick during an audition.
对不起  老朋友
I'm sorry, old friend,
无良的导演不再需要你了
your services are no longer needed.
上帝啊  这么重要的事我居然用电话来结束
Oh, god, I can't believe I'm doing this over the phone!
巴尼一贯甩女人都是用电话
替我向玛吉和孩子们问好
My love to Marge and the kids!
我懂你  给
I know. Here.
-我没意识到会这么痛苦  -我懂我懂
- I didn't realize this would be so hard! - I know, I know.
不过  单子上列的都快搞定了
But hey, you know what? We're almost through our checklist.
-别伤心了  好吗  -好
- Okay? Okay?  - Okay.
正好提醒我了
Which reminds me,
为什么要我打电话给美发沙龙说
why am I calling a hair salon and saying,
妙手杰克要辞职
"Jack Fantastic is quitting"?
甜心
Sweetheart,
就像马雅・安琪罗一直对奥普拉说的
it's like Maya Angelou keeps telling Oprah,
马雅・安琪罗是著名女作家 诗人
我也一直对你说
and I keep telling you:
懂得越多  做得越好
When you know better, you do better.
哇  你好聪明哦
Wow, you are so wise.
真希望你是直男  我们就可以约会了
I wish you were straight so I could date you.
其实吧  我有个非常迷人的
As a matter of fact, I have an extremely attractive
直男双胞胎兄弟
straight twin brother!
你们好啊
Oh hi.
我把万圣节的照片剪了
I cropped that Halloween photo.
只剩盐和胡椒了  看起来荒谬至极
It's just salt and pepper, now, so it looks ridiculous.
-泰德  我要你回到护子队  -什么
- Ted, I want you back on Team Baby. - What?
我就知道你会回心转意的
I knew you'd come around!
伙计们  其实我没有把照片剪掉
Guys! I didn't really crop the photo!
好消息
Good news.
我为咱们报了分娩课程班
I signed us up for a birthing class.
你疯了吧你
Well, that's insane.
现在太早了  是吧  马修
It's way too early for that, right, Marshall?
好吧  听着  我是孩子他爹
Okay, listen. I am the father of this child,
我赞成去上分娩课
and I vote that we go to the birthing class.
想都别想
Absolutely not.
好吧  莉莉
'Kay, Lily.
是你逼我出手的
I hate to play this card...
如果你不去上课
but if you don't come to this class...
我就在床上罢工
I'm withholding sex.
我想她不会来了
I don't think she's coming.
是啊
Yeah.
她提出分开坐计程车时  我就有点儿怀疑了
I was a little suspicious when she had us take separate cabs.
莉莉  别吃
Lily, don't do it!
亲  就一点点哦
Just a little bit.
想想我们的孩子
Think about our baby!
你耍我是吧  罗宾  快说打人的事
You got to be kidding me, Robin. Get to the assault.
好的
Okay, fine.
巴尼和我把公寓收拾好了
So Barney and I were finishing packing his apartment...
好了  单子上的最后一项
Okay. One last item on the checklist.
切断随机电话5000号
Disconnect the Cold Call 5000.
这又玩的哪一出
What the hell's that?
我曾从一家专卖身体闪粉和高档乳贴的
I was able to secure the customer database from a company
公司搞到些客户资料
that sells body glitter and high-end pasties.
随机电话5000号会打给每一个
The Cold Call 5000 will dial every female client
22到23岁的女性客户
between the ages of 22 and 23,
并留下这段留言
and leave the following message:
你好  我知道这太疯狂了
Hi, I know this is crazy,
但我在地铁上对你一见倾心
but I saw you on the subway,
我知道这是命中注定的缘分
and I knew we were meant to be.
如果你相信天意  今晚到麦凯伦酒吧
If you believe in destiny, come to MacLaren's tonight
找我巴尼・斯丁森
and find me, Barney Stinson.
因为我有强烈的感觉  我应该长驱直入你
Because I have this feeling that I'm supposed to be on you--
你的心
with you.
为什么不重录一个正常版的
Why not re-record it?
我试了上百遍了  一录就不由自主说这话
I did like a hundred takes. It kept happening.
真不敢相信莉莉居然不来
I can't believe Lily's not coming!
见鬼去吧
You know what? Screw it!
谁说俩爷们就不能玩转分娩课了
Who says that two bros can't rock a birthing class?
玩转它
Rock it!
今天  我们来研究"肉欲马杀鸡"
Today, we'll be exploring "The Sensual Massage."
首先  请与搭档的手合在一起
Let's start by gently cupping our partner's hands...
感受彼此的呼吸
and just breathe each other in.
谢谢了  罗宾
Thanks, Robin.
我认识的人当中  只有你会帮我收拾这个残局
You're the only person I know who would help me do all that.
你是真兄弟
You're a real bro.
是吗
Am I, though?
女人不能算兄弟吧
'Cause I'm really more of a woman.
敬我的妩媚
To my femininity.
不  你更像兄弟
Nah, you're more of a bro.
你是哥们  是男人
You're a dude. You're a man.
你还可以享受一晚单身
Hey, you are flying solo one more night.
不如我换一件惹火的晚装
How about I put on a smokin' hot dress,
你穿上件能遮住这条煞风景的领带的马甲
you slap a vest over that crime scene of a tie
我们好好乐一下
and we paint the town?
我的意思是  我们多久没以帅哥美女之姿
I mean, when was the last time we got rip-roaring drunk
出来畅饮一番了
in clothing that highlights our genders?
所以你的计划是外出狂欢
So, your plan was to be out on the town,
穿着暴露
dressed provocatively,
以小三的身份陪他喝酒
drinking with another woman's man.
罗宾  这是第一次治疗
Robin, this is our first session, and
纯属临床意见  不过
I know this is just one clinical opinion, but...
高招啊
you a dawg!
是啊
Yeah...
就是有一个问题
There was just one problem...
惊喜吧
Surprise!
我提前回来了
I got back early!
让我猜猜
Let me guess,
又是躲在办公桌下大醉一场吗
you got drunk under your desk again?
不  哈佛先生
No, Mr. Harvard.
我处理的方式有所改变
I handled things a little differently...
我想现在  你会希望我谈谈看着巴尼与诺拉
So, I suppose now you want me to talk about how it felt
双双离开的感觉  对吗
watching Barney and Nora walk off together, right?
我更希望你直接跳到打人的正题
I'd rather just skip ahead to the assault.
我的下一位病人觉得他是上帝
My next patient thinks he's God.
说不定他是对的
On the off chance that he's right,
我可不想让上帝等着
I really don't want to keep him waiting.
他们离开后  劲爆的事情发生了
Well, right after they left, something crazy happened.
打扰下  知道在哪里可以找到巴尼・斯丁森吗
Excuse me, do you know where I can find Barney Stinson?
他在地铁对我一见倾心
He saw me on the subway
并给我留言让我来这里
and left me a message to meet him here.
为什么不重录一个正常版的
Why not re-record it?
我试了上百遍了  一录就不由自主说这话
I did like a hundred takes. It kept happening.
你好  我知道这太疯狂了
Hi, I know this is crazy,
但我在地铁上对你一见倾心
but I saw you on the subway...
他问我是否相信天意  我信
He asked me if I believed in destiny. And I do.
我们果然是命中注定的一对
We are so meant to be.
他在哪里
Where can I find him?
在道义上  我真是进退两难
So I was faced with a moral dilemma.
是让这傻妞去坏他们好事
Unleash this nut bag on them
还是风度一点  帮助我的朋友
or be a bigger person, and help my friend.
巴尼在真爱餐厅  75大街和阿姆斯特丹大街交汇处
Barney's at Café L'Amour, 75th and Amsterdam.
-太好了  -不  等等
- Awesome! - No, wait, wait, wait!
这样不对
Okay, this isn't right.
解开上面的纽扣  秀出你的本钱
Let's pop that top button, show off your gals.
祝你好运  冲吧
Ooh! Good luck, go get 'em!
让你的爱从指间流出
Let your love come through your fingers.
兄弟  规矩是不能哼哼
Dude, the rule is no moaning
而且要一直把眼睛睁着
and keep your eyes open at all times.
正常点
Stop being weird.
什么时候才轮到我当女人
And hey, when do I get to be the woman?
记住  怀孕过程最重要的
Now remember, the most important thing in pregnancy
就是让妈妈平静开心
is to keep Mom calm and happy.
她才知道自己最想要什么
She knows best what she needs.
要信任她
Trust her.
下面有请准爸爸
Now, Papas,
拉住准妈妈的手
I want you to take Mom's hands in yours,
深情地看着她的眼睛
look deep into her eyes,
跟我念
and repeat after me.
我相信你
I believe in you.
我尊敬你的身体智慧
I honor your body's wisdom.
你的子宫就像一座庙宇
Your womb is a temple.
-你的子宫就像一座  -好啦  我知道了
- Your womb is a-- - Okay, I get it!
我们忽视莉莉的意愿  让我觉得好糟糕
I feel terrible we didn't listen to what Lily wanted!
我知道  我也是
I know, so do I.
其实  我一直以为结婚的会是我
The truth is, I thought I'd be married by now
而你们会陪着我一起经历这些事情
and going through all this stuff alongside you guys.
但即使我现在就遇到我的梦中情人
But even if I meet the girl of my dreams right this second,
我离我自己的小家庭
I'm still one night and nine months away
还有一晚和九个月之遥
from having a family of my own.
除非我孩子的妈是个荡妇
And that's assuming the mother of my children
否则很难一见面就上床
is just a huge slut.
不要失去希望  泰德
Don't lose hope, Ted.
那个荡妇在等着你呢
That slut is out there.
谢谢  伙计
Thanks, buddy.
我们该去跟莉莉道歉
We owe Lily an apology.
对
Yeah.
准爸爸  现在是提问时间
Dads, this is the time that I'll answer
你们有什么关于阴道的问题尽管问吧
every question you've ever had about vaginas.
擦  赶巧了
Damn it!
真的很抱歉  莉莉
I'm so sorry, Lily.
亲  就一点点哦
You have just a little bit.
我明白从现在开始的七个月里
I realize now that it's my job for the next seven months
我的职责就是要让你开心  所以
to keep you happy, and that's why...
我会床上当一台永动机
I'm no longer withholding sex.
真英雄
My hero.
但我想确定你也能和桑娅医生相处融洽
But I want to make sure that you feel comfortable with Dr. Sonya, too.
我能  而且我觉得
I do. And you know what,
她这么淡定从容
the fact that she's so calm and laid back,
或许也不是件坏事
maybe that's not a bad thing.
或许我们在分娩的时候
Maybe that's exactly what we're gonna
正需要她这种人才呢
want in that delivery room.
莉莉  如果你不使劲
Lily, if you don't push,
我会把你的宝宝挤上你的喉咙
I will shove this baby up your throat
然后从你的嘴巴拽出来
and pull it out of your mouth!
马修死哪儿去了
Where the hell is Marshall?!
孩子们  这可是个疯狂的故事
That's a crazy story, kids.
晚点会讲到的
I'll get to that.
泰德就在走廊等着呢
Hey, Ted's out in the hall.
他也想向你道歉
He wants to apologize, too.
你的袜子哪儿去了
What happened to your sock?
说来话长
Long story.
总之  我意识到有时
Bottom line, I realized that sometimes
爱意味着放手成全
love means taking a step back.
不尽然吧
Well, not always.
我是说  有时蓄意干扰
I mean, sometimes it's better to interfere
搞点小破坏会更好  不是吗
and sabotage stuff, right?
我觉得如果你真的在乎某人
Well, I think if you care about somebody,
即使你最后被人遗忘
you should want them to be happy,
你还是希望他们能够开心
even if you wind up being left out.
你从马修和莉莉身上得到的感悟
The lesson you learned with Lily and Marshall
整好适用于我现在的情况
is directly applicable to my situation,
因此也是
and is therefore
我最终讲述这个故事时  要说到的一个有用的细节
a valid part of how I'll eventually tell this story.
真的吗
Really?
所以这两件事就联系上了
That's how that went down?
重点就是  环环相扣嘛  对吧
Point is, it all tied together, right?
完全不觉得
Not really at all.
能不能直接说打人的部分
Can we just get to the assault?
敬我们
To us!
巴尼  是我
Barney, it's me!
我爱你  巴尼
I love you, Barney!
扇贝看起来不错
Mmm, scallops look good.
是不错
Oh, they are.
但上次我来这儿时  他们卖完了  所以
But the last time I was here they ran out, so, uh...
祝  你  好  运
knock... on... wood.
Knock on wood 是指接触木制的东西可以甩掉坏运气并确保好运
我要点红丝绒蛋糕作餐后甜点
Well, I have my eye on the red velvet cake for dessert.
很好  一人一口吗
Lovely. Splitsies?
不  我要吃独食
Nah, I want it all toyself.
真的吗
Really?
掰手腕决胜负吧
Arm wrestle for it?
不要
No!
好吧
fine
我爱这家餐厅
I love this place.
-谢谢你  宝贝  -不客气
- Thank you, babe. - You're welcome.
宝贝
Babe.
巴尼对这件事一无所知
Barney doesn't know a thing about any of this.
但这就是我被法院强制接受心理治疗的原因
But that's why I got court-mandated therapy.
你肯定觉得我是个疯婆子
You must think I'm nuts.
我觉得你是一位讲义气的好朋友
I think you're a really good friend.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
依我看来  本次袭击事件绝无犯罪意图
As far as I'm concerned, there was no criminal intent to this assault.
谢谢你  医生
Well, thanks, Doc!
瞧瞧
Well, look at us!
一个疗程解决所有问题
We got this wrapped up in one session.
太牛了  对吧
Go us, right?
下面我们再来谈谈你是怎么弄开法官的车的
Now let's discuss how you keyed the judge's car.
好吧
Okay. Um...
事情是这样的
Here's how it happened:
马修和莉莉本来要一起去动物园
Marshall and Lily were supposed to go to the zoo--
好啦  这都是环环相扣的  我保证
okay, it all ties together, I swear. Now...
1997年
盐和胡椒  以及孜然
1998年
淑女狗与流浪狗  以及装意大利面的盘子
《Lady and the Tramp》是迪斯尼1995年出品的经典动画长片
《Lewis and Clark: A Prairie Dog for the President》著名儿童读物
2000年
刘易斯和克拉克  以及他们的独木舟
2006年
弗兰肯斯坦博士和科学怪人  以及被吓坏的村民
美国1931年经典电影《Frankenstein》
2007年
C-3PO和R2-D2  以及卢克的舅舅差点从加哇人手里买的破机器人
经典科幻电影《Star Wars》